Indiana University Office of State Relations Assistant Director's Records, 1988-1998 C177
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University Office of State Relations Assistant Director's Records
1988-1998
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. Office of State Relations
C177
1 cubic foot 1 box
A system-wide administrative office, the Office of State Relations (OSR) monitors and reacts to state government activities that influence operations at Indiana University. Collection consists of one cubic foot of records created and/or saved by Malcolm M. Webb during his tenure as Assistant Director of the Office of State Relations. Within the folders researchers can find correspondence, faxes, memos, and reports sent and received by Webb. The most prominent subject of the collection, consisting of 11 folders, deal with the early development of the Theatre/Neal-Marshall Center.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Historical Note
A system-wide administrative office, the Office of State Relations (OSR) monitors and reacts to state government activities that influence operations at Indiana University. In this function, the office maintains a close watch on the state's executive branch, the Indiana General Assembly, the State Budget agency, and the Commission for Higher Education. Additionally, the office provides information to the university community, external agencies, and legislators. Throughout its history the office has functioned under numerous offices, but most recently it reports to the President's Office.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of one cubic foot of records created and/or saved by Malcolm Webb during his tenure as Assistant Director of the Office of State Relations. It is organized in a single series, Subject files, and is arranged alphabetically. Within the folders researchers can find correspondence, faxes, memos, and reports sent and created on the particular subject. The most prominent subject of the collection, consisting of 11 folders, deals with the early development of the Theatre/Neal-Marshall Center.
Separated Material
Photographs transferred to the University Archives Photographs Collection.
Oversized "House Resolutions" on the 175th anniversary of the University filed with Archives oversized materials.
Acquisition Information
Accession 98/036
Universities and colleges --Public relations --Indiana --Sources; Neal-Marshall Black Culture Center (Indiana University, Bloomington); Webb, Malcolm McGibbon -- Archives; Indiana University. Office of State Relations -- Archives; Indiana University. Office of State Relations -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University Theater -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Indiana University -- public relations -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Webb, Malcolm McGibbon -- Correspondence
- Subject files, 1988-1998
  - 175th Anniversary and inauguration
    - Folder 1, 1994-1995
    - Folder 2, 1994-1995
  - 175th Resolutions, 1995
  - Beta Theta Pi correspondence, 1993-1994
  - Cultural events, 1995
  - Equity Coalition, 1996
  - Galyan, Connie, 1995
  - GLB Office, 1994-1997
  - Goals: State Relations, 1994-1998
  - Day, Dorothy, Julie Esparza, Kay Flatten and Michael Ney."Indiana University Office of State Relations: Information Management Utilization", 1992
    General
    Paper prepared by SLIS students
  - Inquiries and requests - State officials, 1993-1996
  - IT efforts in tracking legislation - Bill Trading System, 1993
  - Kinsey Institute
    - 1995-1998
    - Concerned Women of America and Burton resolution, 1997-1998
  - Legislative correspondence, 1993-1996
  - Legislative system access - Storage and Information Retrieval System (STAIRS), 1988
  - One N. Capital - computer network, 1995
  - Opera, 1994
  - Planning - Government relations review, 1992-1994
  - State Budget Committee
    - Visit
      - 1993
      - 1995
      - 1997
    - Education program, 1997
    - Lunch at Foster Quad, 1997
    - Tech demo, 1997
    - Zagreb's, 1997
  - Tech Day event, 1996-1997
  - Theatre/Neal-Marshall Center
    - Background
      - 1995-1996
      - 1989-1995
    - Black Cultural Center, 1992-1995
    - Committee, 1995-1996
    - Correspondence, 1996
    - Event, 1995
    - Latest documents, 1995-1996
    - Presentation, 1995
    - Propaganda, 1995
    - Schematic design, 1990
    - Q & A, 1995